She Can Resist Everything But Temptation
Personal Demons is a drama film directed by Brinke Stevens.
An actress recently released from a mental institution inherits a
mansion where she's forced to face her haunting past.
Pandora, played by Brinke Stevens.
Richmond, played by Linnea Quigley.
Dr. Howard, played by Debbie Rochon.
Demon, played by Aaron Gaffey.
Humbert, played by William Butler.
Asylum Doctor, played by Joe Castro.
Demon is a 2015 Polish supernatural psychological horror film
produced, written and directed by Marcin Wrona.
It was shown in the Vanguard section of the 2015
Toronto International Film Festival.
It was Wrona's last feature film, as he died by suicide on 19 September
2015 while promoting the film at the Gdynia Film Festival.